<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SPADE</string>

    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <!-- Strings used for development of this project -->
    <string name="welcomeText">Welcome to the Stool PArasite DEtector \n(SPADE)</string>
    <string name="poweredByCEU">Powered by San Pablo CEU University</string>
    <string name="appExplanationText">This App allows the user to submit images taken with a
        microscope, in order to detect the presence of enteric parasites in human stool samples.
        This App is intended to help in coprological analysis.</string>
    <string name="startButtonText">START</string>
    <string name="howItWorksButtonText">HOW IT WORKS</string>
    <string name="listOfParasitesButtonText">LIST OF PARASITES</string>
    <string name="howItWorksText">This App makes use of a machine learning algorithm to automatically
        detect parasites in stool samples. \n\nThe App requires a .jpg image taken at 40x, which is
        sent to the algorithm in order to be meticulously analysed and processed. If everything goes
        according to plan, you will see the same picture displayed, but with annotations surrounding
        the microorganisms which were found by the algorithm. \n\nAfter that, the annotated image
        will be saved to a database for research purposes, and you can also save it to your Camera
        Roll!</string>
    <string name="listOfParasitesIntroductionText">This App, with the use of machine learning
        technology, can detect many different species of parasites that are occasionally present
        in human stool.</string>
    <string name="CDCWebsite"><a href="https://www.cdc.gov/dpdx/az.html">To see detailed information
        about these fascinating little organisms, go check them out at:
        \nhttps://www.cdc.gov/dpdx/az.html</a></string>
    <string name="backButtonText">BACK</string>
    <string name="loadingText">Your image is being processed, please wait…</string>
    <string name="licenseButtonText">LICENSE</string>
    <string name="licenseText">MIT License\n\nCopyright © 2022 Ricardo Oriol Rocabert\n\n
        Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
        of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
        in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
        to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
        copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
        furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:\n\n
        The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
        copies or substantial portions of the Software.\n\n
        THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
        IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
        FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
        AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
        LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
        OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
        SOFTWARE.</string>
    <string name="fortyX">40X</string>

</resources>